gunssavelives.net 2018-12-20

# Privacy Policy & Terms of Use | Guns Save Lives

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you fill out a form. This information includes any fields filled out on the form as well as your IP address.

We collect information when you comment on an article. This information includes any fields filled out on the form as well as your IP address. Your name and comment content will be displayed publicly.

_Google_

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To improve our website  _(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)_
  * To respond to requests submitted by you such as requests for contact or advertising
  * When using our commenting system, your name and comment content will be displayed publicly. Your email address and IP address will be stored privately, in our database.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. Information is stored in a secure database, on a secured server hosted with a trusted hosting provider.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and make sure redundant information is not displayed.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms of Use**

Comments made on our website are moderated at the discretion of the editorial team. Comments which are racist, violent or which contain excessive profanity will not be allowed. Users who regularly disregard the above comment policy will be banned from further commenting on the site.

As this is a privately owned website, any user may be banned from commenting for any reason. You may or may not receive a warning. You may be banned simply because an editor doesn’t like what you have to say.

Not all comments will be published. We reserve the right to only publish comments which meet our internal guidelines and the guidelines of our sponsors. Only a small percentage of the comments we receive meet our guidelines and are actually published. Most comments are not published. 

Please use clean language, non-racist language, non-violent language and contribute to the topic of the article to increase the chances of having your comment published.

Some regular users have been white listed, which means their comments may appear without being moderated. If a white listed user repeatedly breaks the above policies, they can also be banned without warning.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy and terms of use. These terms may be ammended at any time and for any reason. It is the responsibility of the user to monitor the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use for changes.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

GunsSaveLives.net  
2126 Easy Victory Dr. Suite 138  
Savannah, GA 31401  
admin@gunssavelives.wpengine.com
